Local 1199 Records 5510
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Riverhead Nursing Home, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Rockville Nursing Center [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Rockville Nursing Center [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1959-1972 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1959-1972 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1959-1972 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Ross Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Ross Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Saddlebrook Convalescent Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Saddlebrook Convalescent Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- St. Barnabas Hospital for Chronic Diseases [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1971 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- St. Barnabas Hospital for Chronic Diseases [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1971 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- St. Barnabas Hospital for Chronic Diseases [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1971 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- St. Barnabas Medical Center [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- St. Barnabas Medical Center [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- St. Clare's Hospital, 1960-1964 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- St. John's Episcopal Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- St. John's Episcopal Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- St. John's Episcopal Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- St. John's Episcopal Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- St. John's Queens Hospital, 1969-1972 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- St. John's Smithtown Hospital, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- St. Luke's Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1963 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- St. Luke's Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1959-1963 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- St. Mary's Home for the Aged, 1970-1972 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- St. Mary's Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- St. Mary's Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- St. Michael's Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- St. Michael's Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- St. Michael's Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- St. Vincent's Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1972 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- St. Vincent's Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1972 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Sawmill River Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Sawmill River Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Sayville Nursing Home, 1969-1972 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Schember Organization, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Seagirt Village, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Seaside Convalescent Home, 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Sephardic Home for the Aged, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1971 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Sephardic Home for the Aged, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1971 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- Servomation Mathias, Pa., 1972 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Smithtown Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1972 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Smithtown Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1972 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- So. Carolina Medical College, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- South Oaks Psychiatric Hospital, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Southampton Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1972 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Southampton Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1972 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Southport Manor Convalescent Home, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Southside Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Southside Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Springfield Geri Care, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Staten Island Hospital, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Stoney Brook Hospital, 1970-1972 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Stratford Chronic & Convalescent Hospital, 1968-1972 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Stula Convalescent Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Sunrise Manor Nursing Home, 1971-1972 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Syosset Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1972 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Syosset Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1972 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Terminal Cleaning Contractors, 1965-1970 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Todd Nursing Home, 1970-1971 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Trafalgar Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Trafalgar Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Trafalgar Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Trenton Window Cleaning Co., 1970 (Box 79, Folder 5a)
- United Odd Fellows Home [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1971 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- United Odd Fellows Home [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1971 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- United Presbyterian Residence, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- United Home for Aged Hebrews, 1967-1972 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- United Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1972 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- United Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1972 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- University of Bridgeport, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Walson Army Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Walson Army Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Warburg Lutheran Nursing Home (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Waterbury Hospital, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- West Hampton Nursing Home, 1967-1972 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- West Haven Manor Convalescent Home, 1968-1972 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Westport Manor Convalescent Center, 1968-1972 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Woodbury Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1972 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Woodland Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1972 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Workmen's Circle Home [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1971 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Workmen's Circle Home [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1971 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Wyckoff Heights Hospital, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Wyndover Nursing Home, 1969-1972 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Yeshiva University, 1970-1972 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Yonkers Professional Hospital, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Alps Manor Nursing Home, 1962-1960 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Amcare Center, Inc., 1969 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Arlington Manor Nursing Home, 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Bellevue Hospital, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Berkeley Hall Nursing Home, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Beth Abraham Home, 1961-1963 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Beth Israel, 1963-1969 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Beth-el Hospital, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 8a)
- Bridgeport Nursing Home, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Bronx-Lebanon, 1962-1970 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Brookdale Hospital Center, 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Brooklyn-Cumberland Hospital, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Eye & Ear Hospital, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Brookside Nursing Home, 1960-1967 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Brookwood Convalescent Home, 1968-1970 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Brunswick Park Nursing Home, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Buckley Convalescent Home, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Cedar Manor Nursing Home, 1967-1973 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- Center for Reproductive Health, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 19)
- Clara Maas Memorial Hospital, 1960-1969 (Box 81, Folder 20)
- Columbia University, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 21)
- Community Hospital of Brooklyn, 1960-1968 (Box 81, Folder 22)
- Daughters of Israel, 1960-1971 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Daughters of Israel Pleasant Home, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Daughters of Jacob Home, 1960-1967 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Daughters of Miriam Home, 1965-1967 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Dr. Friedman's Convalescent Home, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Doctor's Hospital, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 5a)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital Association, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Elizabeth Manor Nursing Home, 1965-1969 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Elmwood Manor Nursing Home, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Evangelical Deaconess Hospital, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Evangelical Home for the Aged, 1969-1973 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- First United Lemberger Home, 1961-1963 (Box 82, Folder 10a)
- Flushing Hospital & Medical Center, 1960-1969 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Forest Manor Health Related Facility, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Freeport Hospital, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- French Benevolent Society, 1962-1967 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- French Hospital, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Garret Food Management, Inc., 1965 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- Gouverneur Beth Israel, 1963-1967 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Gracie Square Hospital, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 17a)
- Graham Home for Old Ladies, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Harlem Eye & Ear Hospital, 1967-1969 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Hawkes Ambulance Service, Inc., 1961 (Box 82, Folder 20)
- Haym-Salomon, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 21)
- Health Ins. Plan of Greater NY, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 22)
- Hebrew Convalescent Home, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 22a)
- Helene Fuld, 1965-1968 (Box 82, Folder 23)
- Hempstead General Hospital, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 24)
- Hilaire Farm Nursing Home, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 25)
- Home for Aged & Infirm Hebrews, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 26)
- Home of Old Israel, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 26a)
- Home of Sons & Daughters of Israel, 1961-1963 (Box 82, Folder 27)
- Hospital Center at Orange, 1960-1969 (Box 82, Folder 28)
- Hospital Dietetics Inc., 1969 (Box 82, Folder 29)
- Hospital of Jacques Loewe Found., 1962 (Box 82, Folder 30)
- Manhasset Medical Center Hospital (Box 83.1, Folder 5)
- Maimonides Hospital (Box 83.1, Folder 4)
- Lutheran Medical Center (Box 83.1, Folder 3)
- Long Island Jewish (Box 83.1, Folder 2)
- Long Island Doctors Hospital (Box 83.1, Folder 1)
- Manhattan Eye, Ear + Throat (Box 83.1, Folder 6)
- Hospital Parking Co. of America [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1973 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Hospital Parking Co. of America [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1973 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Hospital Parking Co. of America [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1973 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- House of Holy Comforter, 1964-1968 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Irvington Nursing Home, 1962-1965 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Jewish Chronic Disease Hospital, 1961-1963 (Box 83, Folder 5a)
- Jewish Home & Hospital for Aged, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Jewish Hospital and Rehabilitation Center of New Jersey, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Jewish Memorial Hospital, 1966-1969 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Joint Disease Hospital, 1964-1966 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Kingsbrook Hospital-, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Knickerbocker Hospital, 1964-1967 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Lakeside Hospital, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- League of Voluntary Hospitals, 1968-1970 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Lemberger Home for Aged, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- Lenox Hill Hospital, 1963-1966 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Long Island Doctor's Hospital, 1964-1972 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital, 1963-1970 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Lutheran Medical Center, 1963-1970 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Maimonides Hospital, 1957-1970 (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Manhasset Medical Center Hospital, 1960-1969 (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Manhattan Eye, Ear & Throat Hospital, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 22)
- Margaret Sanger Res. Bureau, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Mary Manning Walsh Home, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Methadone Counselors Union, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Modern Maintenance Inc., 1960-1970 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Modern Maintenance, Inc., Montclair, 1968-1970 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Montefiore Hospital, 1959-1969 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Mt. Morris Park Hospital, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital, 1963-1969 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Mt. Sinai James Felt & Associates, 1960-1965 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Nassau Hospital Association, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- National Food Management Services, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Neighborhood Maternity Center, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Neustadter Convalescent Home, 1965-1971 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- New Jersey Infirmary, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- New York Medical College, Flower Fifth, 1966-1969 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- NYU Medical Center, 1968-1970 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Newark Gardens Convalescent Sanitorium, 1962-1968 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Northfield Manor Nursing Home, 1965-1968 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Parker Laura Nursing Home, 1965-1968 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- Parkway Nursing Home, 1965-1968 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Pine Acres Nursing Home, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Pine Haven Nursing Home, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Prophet Foods Co.., 1971 (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Public Health Research Institute:, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 24)
- Restaurant Associates Industries, 1970-1972 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Richmond of N.J., 1970 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Rockville Nursing Center, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Ross Nursing Home, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Saddle Brook Convalescent Home, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- St. Barnabas Medical Center, 1961-1969 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- St. John's Episcopal Hospital, 1963-1969 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- St. Michael's Medical Center, 1969-1971 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Sayville Nursing Home, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Schember Organization, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Seagirt Village, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Sephardic Home, 1961-1960 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Service Systems Corporation; Columbia Cafeterias, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Shattuck Company, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Southampton Hospital Association, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Stratford Chronic and Convalescent Hospital, 1968-1971 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- Syosset Hospital, 1961-1969 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- Terminal Cleaning and Contractor [folder 1 of 5], 1960-1973 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- Terminal Cleaning and Contractor [folder 2 of 5], 1960-1973 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Terminal Cleaning and Contractor [folder 3 of 5], 1960-1973 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Terminal Cleaning and Contractor [folder 4 of 5], 1960-1973 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- Terminal Cleaning and Contractor [folder 5 of 5], 1960-1973 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- Trafalgar Hospital, 1960-1969 (Box 85, Folder 23)
- United Odd Fellows Home, 1960-1961 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- Unity Hospital, 1962-1966 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- West Haven Manor, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 26)
- Woodbury Nursing Home, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 27)
- Workmen's Circle Old Age Home, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 28)
- Wyndover Convalescent Hospital, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 29)
- Bronx Area [folder 1 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Bronx Area [folder 2 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Bronx Area [folder 3 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Bronx Area [folder 4 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Bronx Area [folder 5 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Bronx Area [folder 6 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Bronx Area [folder 7 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Bronx Area [folder 8 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Bronx Area [folder 9 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Bronx Area [folder 10 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Bronx Area [folder 11 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Bronx Area [folder 12 of 12], 1963-1972 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 1 of 14], 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 2 of 14], 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 3 of 14], 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 4 of 14], 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 5 of 14], 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 6 of 14], 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 7 of 14], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 8 of 14], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 9 of 14], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 10 of 14], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 11 of 14], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 12 of 14], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 13 of 14], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Area [folder 14 of 14], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Connecticut Area [folder 1 of 3], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Connecticut Area [folder 2 of 3], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Connecticut Area [folder 3 of 3], 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Downtown Area [folder 1 of 8], 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Downtown Area [folder 2 of 8], 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Downtown Area [folder 3 of 8], 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Downtown Area [folder 4 of 8], 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Downtown Area [folder 5 of 8], 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Downtown Area [folder 6 of 8], 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Downtown Area [folder 7 of 8], 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Downtown Area [folder 8 of 8], 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- New Jersey Area [folder 1 of 7], 1963-1972 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- New Jersey Area [folder 2 of 7], 1963-1972 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- New Jersey Area [folder 3 of 7], 1963-1972 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- New Jersey Area [folder 4 of 7], 1963-1972 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- New Jersey Area [folder 5 of 7], 1963-1972 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- New Jersey Area [folder 6 of 7], 1963-1972 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- New Jersey Area [folder 7 of 7], 1963-1972 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 1 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 2 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 3 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 4 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 5 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 6 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 7 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 8 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Queens-Long Island Area [folder 9 of 9], 1960-1972 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Uptown Area [folder 1 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Uptown Area [folder 2 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Uptown Area [folder 3 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Uptown Area [folder 4 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Uptown Area [folder 5 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Uptown Area [folder 6 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Uptown Area [folder 7 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Uptown Area [folder 8 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Uptown Area [folder 9 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Uptown Area [folder 10 of 10], 1960-1972 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Booth Memorial Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn Hebrew Home, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Central General Hospital, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Deepdale Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Flushing Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Harlem Eye and Ear Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Hebrew Home for the Aged, 1963-1960 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Hospital for Joint Diseases, 1963-1966 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Hospital for Special Surgery, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- House of the Holy Comforter, 1963-1960 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Jamaica Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Jewish Memorial Hospital, 1962-1964 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Knickerbocker Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- LeRoy Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Long Island College Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Manhattan Eye and Ear Hospital, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Menorah Home and Hospital for Aged, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 18)
- Misericordia Hospital, 1963-1969 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- New York Eye and Ear Infirmary, 1963-1964 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- New York Hospital, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- New York Infirmary, 1963-1960 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Parkway Hospital, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1966-1969 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- St. Barnabas Hospital, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- St. John's Hospital, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- St. Mary's Hospital, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Smithtown General Hospital, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Syosset Hospital, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Wyckoff Heights Hospital, 1963-1964 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous SLRB [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1969 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous SLRB [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1969 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- General Information, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Report [folder 1 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Report [folder 2 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Report [folder 3 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Report [folder 4 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Report [folder 5 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Report [folder 6 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Report [folder 7 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Report [folder 8 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Report [folder 9 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Report [folder 10 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Report [folder 11 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Report [folder 12 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Report [folder 13 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- Report [folder 14 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Report [folder 15 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Report [folder 16 of 16], 1968 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- 1199 Brief for Annual Review, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Annual Review, 1960-1962 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- 1199 Brief for Annual Review, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Analysis of Annual Review, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Report on Volunteer Hospitals, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Strike and PAC Material, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Hearing, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Brief Hearing, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Amended Statement of Policy, 1960-1962 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- PAC Letters to Hospitals, A-I, 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- PAC Letters to Hospitals, J-Q, 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- PAC Letters to Hospitals, R-Z, 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- N.Y.S. Minimum Wage, Unemployment Insurance, Disability Insurance, Collective Bargaining Rights for Employees of Non-Profit Institutions, 1959-1960 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage, Unemployment Insurance, Amend State Labor Relations Law to include Non-Profit Institution Employees, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage, Albert McCloskey Bill, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Bill to Extend Collective Bargaining Rights in NYC with a Ban on Strikes and Provision for Binding Arbitration, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Bill to Eliminate Literacy Tests as Basis for Right to Vote, Removal of Exemption on Non-Profit Institutions from the Anti-Discrimination Law re Hiring Practices, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Health Insurance Plans, Extension of Collective Bargaining Rights to Employees in Voluntary Non-Profit Hospitals Throughout the State (Warner Bill), 1965 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Acts to Amend Labor Law in Hospitals (Printed Bills), 1963-1965 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Votes on Hospital Labor Bills in Senate, Assembly, 1961-1965 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Legislative Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1957-1961 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Health Insurance Plans, Joint Legislative Committee (Statements and Related Documents), 1961 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Legislation - Unemployment Insurance, Workmen's Compensation, 1957-1966 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- 1199 Statement on Position of N.Y.S. AFL-CIO re Legislation for Hospital Workers, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Amended Statement of Policy, 1960-1961 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Meany's Statement re Hospital Organizing, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Citizen's Committee - N.Y.S. AFL-CIO Albert-McCloskey Bill, 1961-1963 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Citizen's Committee for Equal Rights -Letters on Legislation - Albert McCloskey Bill, 1961-1963 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Hospital - State Labor Laws (Minnesota, Wisconsin, etc.), 1956-1964 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Legislation (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Hospital Division Delegates Newsletter, 1971-1972 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Greater New York Hospital Association. Form letters, minutes, memos, and correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Correspondence re James Lucas. (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Wages Rates, 1959 (Box 101a, Folder 1)
- Wage Scales, Rates. (Box 101a, Folder 2)
- Blue Cross-American Hospital Association, 1959-1964 (Box 101a, Folder 3)
- Annual Reports (financial) to department of Social Welfare, 1961 (Box 101a, Folder 4)
- Local 1199 Hospital News, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Meeting notices (council and stewards meetings and rally notices), 1962-1963 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Training classes for stewards, 1960 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Union builders contest, 1960 (Box 102, Folder 4)